csra.com 2017-01-30

# Privacy Policy | CSRA

### CSRA's Section 508 Compliance Policy

In 1998, Congress amended the Rehabilitation Act to require Federal agencies to make their electronic and information technology accessible to people with disabilities. Inaccessible technology interferes with an individual’s ability to obtain and use information quickly and easily. CSRA recognizes and acknowledges the requirement for compliance with Section 508 of the Rehabilitation Act and the Accessibility standards within 36 CFR part 1194.

### CSRA Online Privacy Notice

_Effective December 1, 2015._  
We are very sensitive to privacy issues.   CSRA has adopted this Privacy Notice to let you know how we handle the information we receive from you through this Site and to assure you of our commitment and dedication to privacy so that you can make an informed decision as to whether and to what extent to disclose personal information.

The following Privacy Notice applies to the Web site "www.csra.com" (Site). This Privacy Notice does not apply to information collected offline or via online sources other than the Site. We invite you to visit the Site to search or browse without revealing personal information or registering with CSRA.  However, as we gather information about your usage or as you may choose to give CSRA personal information via the Site, CSRA will let you know how we will use such information and provide you with an option to opt out. Your continued use of the Site will indicate your agreement to this Privacy Notice.

As used in this Privacy Notice, terms such as "we" or "our" refer to CSRA Inc. and its current and future affiliate entities.

### Personal Information Provided by You

When we use the term "personal information," we mean information that specifically identifies you as an individual, such as your full name, telephone number, e-mail address, postal address, or certain account numbers.

To the maximum practical extent, CSRA will collect information directly from the individual. CSRA provides means, where feasible and appropriate, for individuals to authorize the collection, use, maintenance, and sharing for information prior to its collection. CSRA provides appropriate means for individuals to understand the consequences of decisions to approve or decline the authorization of the collection, use, dissemination, and retention of personal information. You do not have to provide us with personal information if you do not want to; however, that may limit your ability to use certain functions of this Site or to request certain services or information.

By providing us with your contact information in order to receive information from CSRA, you are opting in to receiving a communication regarding your inquiry. If you do not wish to be contacted by CSRA, please do not enter any contact information on our Site.

### Uses and Disclosures of Personal Information

Except as described in this Privacy Notice, we will not use your personal information or disclose it to a third party without your consent.   
We may use personal information for a number of purposes such as:

  * To respond to an e-mail or particular request from you;
  * To process an application as requested by you;
  * To comply with applicable laws, regulations, and legal process;
  * To protect someone's health, safety, or welfare;
  * To protect our rights or take appropriate legal action; or
  * As otherwise necessary or useful for us to conduct our business, so long as such use is permitted by law and is consistent with the uses enumerated above.

CSRA collects the minimum information necessary to serve its customers and the general public. Information collected on the Site will only be used for the specific reasons for which it was provided. Information collected from you will not be shared with third parties for purposes other than in support of CSRA's operations and as necessary to facilitate the purpose for which it was provided.

We limit the collection of personal information to what we need to know in order to achieve our goal of providing superior quality and value, and we use personal information only for the purpose for which it was collected. For example, some sections of our Site invite you to contact us for more information, and in these cases we may request your name and email address. We will not use your email for any other purpose, and you will not receive unsolicited e-mail from CSRA as a result of supplying this information.

### Uses and Disclosures of Cookies and Non-Personal Information

The term "non-personal information" means information that does not permit us to specifically identify you by your full name or similar unique identifying information such as a social security number, member identification number, address or telephone number. CSRA uses "cookie" technology and similar technology to gather non-personal information from our Site visitors, such as which pages are used and how often they are used, and to enable certain features on this Site.  
You may disable these cookies and similar items by adjusting your browser preferences on your computer at any time; however, this may limit your ability to take advantage of all the features on this Site. Keep in mind that cookies are not used to collect any personal information and do not tell us who you are. Some examples of the way we use cookies include:

  * Tracking resources and data accessed on the site;
  * Recording general site statistics and activity;
  * Assisting users experiencing Site problems;
  * Enabling certain functions and tools on this Site; and
  * Tracking paths of visitors to this site and within this site.

We may also collect other forms of non-personal information, such as what web browsers are used to read our Site and what other websites are referring traffic or linking to our Site. Aggregate and de-identified data regarding Site users is considered non-personal information.

Because non-personal information does not identify who you are, we do not find it necessary limit the ways we may use or share non-personal information. For example, we may share non-personal information with our affiliates, suppliers, employees and agents, other businesses, and the government.

### Usage Statistics

Whether you register or not, when you visit the Site, some information such as your Internet Protocol (IP) address, Internet service provider, operating system, the service from which you arrived, the page you requested, the time and date of your visit, and potentially other site usage statistics will be collected automatically as part of the software processes of the Web page. This information itself does not personally identify you, but could potentially be linked with personal information that you provide CSRA. These statistics allow CSRA to analyze the effectiveness of its Site, make improvements where needed and potentially to market CSRA's products and services to you. Generally, this information is kept as long as required to support the improvements of the Site and could be shared with our advisors, agents or other third parties.

### Security and Data Integrity

Security is a high priority for CSRA. To protect the personal data you submit to this Site, we have implemented appropriate organizational, technical and physical safeguards to prevent unauthorized access or disclosure. We require the same high standard of information security and information management of any third parties with whom we share your data. Due to the nature of the Internet, we cannot guarantee that unauthorized parties will never be able to defeat those measures or use your personal information for improper purposes; however, this Site takes every precaution to protect our users' information.  
Most e-mail, including any e-mail functionality on our Site, does not provide a completely secure and confidential means of communication. It is possible that your e-mail communication may be accessed or viewed inappropriately by another Internet user while in transit to us. If you wish to keep your information completely private, you should not use e-mail.

### External Links

We furnish external links on CSRA's web pages that cause you to leave our Site.  These are provided for your convenience and should be used with discretion. Please be aware that we have no control over the Internet sites accessible through these links or the information found there. CSRA cannot and does not make any representation about these sites or the material on them. We do not endorse or recommend any of the material or information found on any non-CSRA site. CSRA is not liable for any personal information that you submit to third parties or to any Web site linked to this Site.

### Resume Collection

The Site provides a capability for users to submit their resumes to CSRA via email. Any resume so received by CSRA will be held in confidence and used only for the purpose of considering the submitting party for employment. Such information is not shared with third parties external to CSRA domestic and international branches.

### Children

This Site is intended for adult use only. It is not intended for children, and CSRA asks that minors not submit any personal information.

### Additional Terms

Certain features and services of www.csra.com \- especially highly interactive features - may involve types of personal information and data handling that are not specifically discussed here in this Privacy Notice. Rest assured that this notice applies wherever you go within www.csra.com. We may, however, provide additional privacy information at a particular feature or service so you can be better informed about CSRA's practices, including how that service may be collecting and using your personal information and opportunities you may have to access and correct your information. Additional terms may also explain how this Privacy Notice applies to the particular feature or service.

Any personal information that you provide when using the CSRA Site may be transferred between CSRA business units, subsidiaries and affiliates for the purposes outlined in this Privacy Notice. This applies to all jurisdictions including the European Economic Area and by using the services provided you consent to the transfer of your personal information to CSRA global entities for the limited purposes.

### Contact and Complaint Resolution

CSRA is committed to resolving any complaints you may have in relation to your privacy and CSRA's collection and use of your personal information. Please send any privacy-related complaints or requests, including request for access to information, to [communications@csra.com](mailto:communications@csra.com).

### Changes to the Online Privacy Notice

CSRA reserves the right to change, modify, or update this Notice at any time to reflect changes in practice or policy that affect personal information or changes in activities that impact privacy.  We will provide a summary of any material changes that may affect how we process or use any personal information you previously gave CSRA. Be sure to check this page periodically for updates.
